{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825404367","data":{"timestamp":" 946825404367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 00ef5789-5a48-4828-9bc2-064755e293e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825406768","data":{"timestamp":" 946825406768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 00ef5789-5a48-4828-9bc2-064755e293e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825504371","data":{"timestamp":" 946825504370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 00ef5789-5a48-4828-9bc2-064755e293e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825504426","data":{"timestamp":" 946825504426"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 811aa443-a2df-4e49-a8b9-7052c0632312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825515380","data":{"timestamp":" 946825515379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825521086","data":{"timestamp":" 946825521086"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825522687","data":{"timestamp":" 946825522686"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825525147","data":{"timestamp":" 946825525147"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825526751","data":{"timestamp":" 946825526750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825529329","data":{"timestamp":" 946825529328"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825530903","data":{"timestamp":" 946825530902"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825534134","data":{"timestamp":" 946825534133"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825535718","data":{"timestamp":" 946825535718"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825538915","data":{"timestamp":" 946825538915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825540502","data":{"timestamp":" 946825540501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825552550","data":{"timestamp":" 946825552549"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825554188","data":{"timestamp":" 946825554187"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825556544","data":{"timestamp":" 946825556544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825558565","data":{"timestamp":" 946825558563"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825558672","data":{"timestamp":" 946825558672"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 28202c2b-5204-4f7b-b85f-2b4a1795bf23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825582771","data":{"timestamp":" 946825582770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825587433","data":{"timestamp":" 946825587433"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825593085","data":{"timestamp":" 946825593085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825599276","data":{"timestamp":" 946825599276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825605125","data":{"timestamp":" 946825605125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825609763","data":{"timestamp":" 946825609763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825615220","data":{"timestamp":" 946825615220"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825621302","data":{"timestamp":" 946825621302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825628455","data":{"timestamp":" 946825628455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825638363","data":{"timestamp":" 946825638363"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825643051","data":{"timestamp":" 946825643051"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825648373","data":{"timestamp":" 946825648373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825654991","data":{"timestamp":" 946825654990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 842989e4-5a5c-4f31-8cf1-c9b04b948bcb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825663363","data":{"timestamp":" 946825663363"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_L-O-M"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825683829","data":{"timestamp":" 946825683828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-R-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825719049","data":{"timestamp":" 946825719049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825724403","data":{"timestamp":" 946825724403"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_N-O-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825729414","data":{"timestamp":" 946825729414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_Y-K-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825736318","data":{"timestamp":" 946825736318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_E-O-P"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825741157","data":{"timestamp":" 946825741157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" df4b1ed4-f360-4620-ae24-897ff03e7899"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_O_E-O-P"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825825298","data":{"timestamp":" 946825825297"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825827978","data":{"timestamp":" 946825827978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825861107","data":{"timestamp":" 946825861107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825863294","data":{"timestamp":" 946825863294"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825865567","data":{"timestamp":" 946825865566"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825919247","data":{"timestamp":" 946825919246"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825922013","data":{"timestamp":" 946825922012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825962907","data":{"timestamp":" 946825962905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946825962995","data":{"timestamp":" 946825962995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajua kuwa alilipa nauli yake kamili!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMILI"," userResponse":" KAMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826012977","data":{"timestamp":" 946826012977"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9fa16f83-078a-4f17-bf49-b4dceaa8e894"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anajua kuwa alilipa nauli yake kamili!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826013022","data":{"timestamp":" 946826013022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 0714a06b-e07b-437d-b9b6-444a0b3debc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi Mbwa na Ng'ombe walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826021126","data":{"timestamp":" 946826021125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 0714a06b-e07b-437d-b9b6-444a0b3debc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuzi Mbwa na Ng'ombe walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826036820","data":{"timestamp":" 946826036820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 0714a06b-e07b-437d-b9b6-444a0b3debc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuzi Mbwa na Ng'ombe walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826049428","data":{"timestamp":" 946826049427"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826049810","data":{"timestamp":" 946826049810"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826050306","data":{"timestamp":" 946826050306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826050659","data":{"timestamp":" 946826050658"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826051071","data":{"timestamp":" 946826051070"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826051553","data":{"timestamp":" 946826051553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826051784","data":{"timestamp":" 946826051783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826055027","data":{"timestamp":" 946826055027"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826055071","data":{"timestamp":" 946826055071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826055791","data":{"timestamp":" 946826055791"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826056184","data":{"timestamp":" 946826056184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826056479","data":{"timestamp":" 946826056478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826056682","data":{"timestamp":" 946826056682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826056876","data":{"timestamp":" 946826056876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826057190","data":{"timestamp":" 946826057190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826057414","data":{"timestamp":" 946826057414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826060709","data":{"timestamp":" 946826060708"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826061123","data":{"timestamp":" 946826061122"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826063713","data":{"timestamp":" 946826063713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826063920","data":{"timestamp":" 946826063920"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826064131","data":{"timestamp":" 946826064131"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826067665","data":{"timestamp":" 946826067664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826071499","data":{"timestamp":" 946826071498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826072533","data":{"timestamp":" 946826072532"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826075285","data":{"timestamp":" 946826075285"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826075667","data":{"timestamp":" 946826075665"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826076159","data":{"timestamp":" 946826076159"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826076513","data":{"timestamp":" 946826076512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826076935","data":{"timestamp":" 946826076934"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826077419","data":{"timestamp":" 946826077418"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826077652","data":{"timestamp":" 946826077652"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826080837","data":{"timestamp":" 946826080836"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826080878","data":{"timestamp":" 946826080878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826081620","data":{"timestamp":" 946826081620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826082020","data":{"timestamp":" 946826082020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826082325","data":{"timestamp":" 946826082324"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826082546","data":{"timestamp":" 946826082545"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826082752","data":{"timestamp":" 946826082751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826083082","data":{"timestamp":" 946826083081"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826083316","data":{"timestamp":" 946826083315"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826085968","data":{"timestamp":" 946826085966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826086043","data":{"timestamp":" 946826086043"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" f1b6abd6-8865-4125-a52e-5f0ffc04d02d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826264642","data":{"timestamp":" 946826264642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani_pango-pango-zangu-angani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" angani"," userResponse":" angani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826319306","data":{"timestamp":" 946826319306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua_jua-mto-chakula-wao"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jua"," userResponse":" wao"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826321969","data":{"timestamp":" 946826321969"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua_jua-mto-chakula-wao"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jua"," userResponse":" chakula"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826324647","data":{"timestamp":" 946826324647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua_jua-mto-chakula-wao"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jua"," userResponse":" mto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826327953","data":{"timestamp":" 946826327953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua_jua-mto-chakula-wao"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jua"," userResponse":" jua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826379367","data":{"timestamp":" 946826379367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai_pango-Tai-manyoya-refu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Tai"," userResponse":" pango"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826383265","data":{"timestamp":" 946826383265"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai_pango-Tai-manyoya-refu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Tai"," userResponse":" Tai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826595101","data":{"timestamp":" 946826595101"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" nina"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826602336","data":{"timestamp":" 946826602335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" mbweha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826606021","data":{"timestamp":" 946826606021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" hicho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826608693","data":{"timestamp":" 946826608692"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" mbweha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826611383","data":{"timestamp":" 946826611383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" nina"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826614906","data":{"timestamp":" 946826614906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" nyoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826626874","data":{"timestamp":" 946826626873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nyoka_hicho-mbweha-nina-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826626992","data":{"timestamp":" 946826626991"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" d7af16a0-d33d-4f4b-8ea2-1abe7aa8802e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_27"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826636593","data":{"timestamp":" 946826636593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-M-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826640089","data":{"timestamp":" 946826640089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-O-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826645307","data":{"timestamp":" 946826645307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-O-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826653282","data":{"timestamp":" 946826653281"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_Y-Z-O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826663739","data":{"timestamp":" 946826663739"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-M-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826666442","data":{"timestamp":" 946826666442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_L-O-A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826673263","data":{"timestamp":" 946826673262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 482e269c-0210-445b-9306-57dd5b310773"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_O_L-O-A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826691392","data":{"timestamp":" 946826691392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-8-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826697564","data":{"timestamp":" 946826697564"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826706205","data":{"timestamp":" 946826706204"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826713137","data":{"timestamp":" 946826713137"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826719491","data":{"timestamp":" 946826719491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_7-4-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826726757","data":{"timestamp":" 946826726757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826731908","data":{"timestamp":" 946826731908"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826739421","data":{"timestamp":" 946826739421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-8-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826747259","data":{"timestamp":" 946826747258"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826760010","data":{"timestamp":" 946826760009"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826764528","data":{"timestamp":" 946826764528"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826776297","data":{"timestamp":" 946826776297"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826780850","data":{"timestamp":" 946826780850"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826787401","data":{"timestamp":" 946826787400"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 85108ea7-7585-4448-bbe9-2483beba4dba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826801468","data":{"timestamp":" 946826801468"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9b7fbb32-5209-47c8-8401-a94ef4a472f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826803964","data":{"timestamp":" 946826803964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9b7fbb32-5209-47c8-8401-a94ef4a472f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946826811728","data":{"timestamp":" 946826811728"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_180305"," gameId":" 9b7fbb32-5209-47c8-8401-a94ef4a472f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}